Guide to the Asian CineVision Records TAM.416
Tamiment Library and Robert F. Wagner Labor Archives
- Series III: Video Recordings, 545120
  - Video 576: Unidentified, CCTV labeled "A-4", cuid1839; 545871
  - Video 577: Annual Show, 3rd, CCTV, CCTV labeled "A16", cuid1840; 545870 (Box 128)
  - Video 578: Asian American Dance Theater, CCTV labeled "A-14", cuid1841; 545869 (Box 128)
  - Video 579: Asian American Dance Theater I + II, 2-16-78, CCTV labeled "A-29", cuid1842; 545868 (Box 128)
  - Video 580: Asian American Experience Reel #2: 1. Slide Show Stereotypes Corky Lee, Robin Wu, B. Chu, 2. Intermarriage, CCTV labeled "A19", cuid1843; 545867 (Box 128)
  - Video 581: Film Festival: Fu Ding Cheng, Flight of Ideas, While in Bad Light, Annie Wong, Cracking Up, Women's Rights, Cowboy Fade-Out, Automobile, CCTV labeled "A15", cuid1844; 545866 (Box 128)
  - Video 582: From Division Street to Here (I, II), CCTV labeled A27, cuid1845; 545865 (Box 128)
  - Video 583: CCTV labeled "Final (see inside)", cuid1846; 545864 (Box 128)
  - Video 584: Martha Panel Show (sample), CCTV labeled "A22", cuid1847; 545863 (Box 128)
  - Video 585: Workshop Project 2 Picnic 7/26, Final Tape, CCTV labeled "283", cuid1848; 545862 (Box 128)
  - Video 586: Unidentified (Chinese), CCTV labeled "A-21", cuid1849; 545861 (Box 128)
  - Video 587: Unidentified (Chinese), CCTV labeled "A23", cuid1850; 545860 (Box 128)
  - Video 588: Unidentified (Chinese), CCTV labeled "A24", cuid1851; 545859 (Box 128)
  - Video 589: Unidentified (Chinese) by CT Lui, CCTV labeled "A13", cuid1852; 545858 (Box 128)
  - Video 590: Unidentified, CCTV labeled "139', cuid1853; 545857 (Box 129)
  - Video 591: Unidentified, CCTV labeled "224', cuid1854; 545856 (Box 129)
  - Video 592: Unidentified, CCTV labeled "225", cuid1855; 545855 (Box 129)
  - Video 593: Unidentified, CCTV labeled "226", cuid1856; 545854 (Box 129)
  - Video 594: Unidentified, CCTV labeled "231", cuid1857; 545853 (Box 129)
  - Video 595: Unidentified, CCTV labeled "236", cuid1858; 545852 (Box 129)
  - Video 596: Unidentified, CCTV labeled "240", cuid1859; 545851 (Box 129)
  - Video 597: Unidentified, CCTV labeled "276", cuid1860; 545850 (Box 129)
  - Video 598: Unidentified, CCTV labeled "278", cuid1861; 545849 (Box 129)
  - Video 599: Unidentified, CCTV labeled "279", cuid1862; 545848 (Box 129)
  - Video 600: Unidentified, CCTV labeled "282", cuid1863; 545847 (Box 129)
  - Video 601: Unidentified, CCTV labeled "289", cuid1864; 545846 (Box 130)
  - Video 602: Unidentified, CCTV labeled "293", cuid1865; 545845 (Box 130)
  - Video 603: Unidentified, CCTV labeled "298", cuid1866; 545844 (Box 130)
  - Video 604: Unidentified, CCTV labeled "299", cuid1867; 545843 (Box 130)
  - Video 605: Unidentified, CCTV labeled "A28", cuid1868; 545842 (Box 130)
  - Video 606: Unidentified, cuid1869; 545841 (Box 130)
  - Video 607: Unidentified, cuid1870; 545840 (Box 130)
  - Video 608: Unidentified, cuid1871; 545839 (Box 130)
  - Video 609: Unidentified, cuid1872; 545838 (Box 130)
  - Video 610: Unidentified, cuid1873; 545837 (Box 130)
  - Video 611: Unidentified, cuid1874; 545836 (Box 130)
  - Video 612: Unidentified, cuid1875; 545835 (Box 130)
  - Video 613: Black and White Logo, cuid1876; 545834 (Box 131)
  - Video 614: Color Logo, cuid1877; 545833 (Box 131)
  - Video 615:AAFF 5/12, cuid1878; 545832 (Box 131)
  - Video 616:AAFF Arnie Masako, cuid1879; 545831 (Box 131)
  - Video 617:Even's Interview? Reaction Shot???, cuid1880; 545830 (Box 131)
  - Video 618:Al Stewart: Past, Present and Future, cuid1881; 545829 (Box 131)
  - Video 619: AAIFF 1989 16mm trailer, cuid1882; 545828 (Box 131)
  - Video 620:1988 Logo, cuid1883; 545827 (Box 131)
  - Video 621: Woo Art Asian Cine Vision Graphic Open ACV Presents: 20 Sec. Plus August 23, 1988, cuid1884; 545826 (Box 131)
  - Video 622: Woo Art International, Inc. ACV Opening 07/14/89, cuid1885; 545825 (Box 131)
  - Video 623: Unidentified, Chinese title, cuid1886; 545824 (Box 132)
  - Video 624: Unidentified, Chinese title, cuid1887; 545823 (Box 132)
  - Video 625: Unidentified, Chinese title, cuid1888; 545822 (Box 132)
  - Video 626: Unidentified, Chinese title, cuid1889; 545821 (Box 132)
  - Video 627: Unidentified, Chinese title, cuid1890; 545820 (Box 132)
  - Video 628: Unidentified, Chinese title, cuid1891; 545819 (Box 132)
  - Video 629: Unidentified, Chinese title, cuid1892; 545818 (Box 132)
  - Video 630: Unidentified, Chinese title, cuid1893; 545817 (Box 132)
  - Video 631: Unidentified, Chinese title, cuid1894; 545816 (Box 132)
  - Video 632: Unidentified, Chinese title, cuid1895; 545815 (Box 132)
  - Video 633: Unidentified, Chinese title, cuid1896; 545814 (Box 133)
  - Video 634: Unidentified, CCTV labeled "Asian Cine Vision", cuid1897; 545813 (Box 133)
  - Video 635: Unidentified, "Asian American International Film Festival (AAIFF), 1987, Commercial", cuid1898; 545812 (Box 133)
  - Video 636: Unidentified, CCTV labeled "Camera training tape", cuid1899; 545811 (Box 133)
  - Video 637: Unidentified, CCTV labeled "CCTV logo master", cuid1900; 545810 (Box 133)
  - Video 638: Unidentified, CCTV labeled "Emergency," which served as a backup broadcast tape for CCTV, cuid1901; 545809 (Box 133)
  - Video 639: Unidentified, "'Freckled Rice' and sample logo", cuid1902; 545808 (Box 133)
  - Video 640: Unidentified, CCTV labeled "Mew Jail in Chinatown CCTV production", cuid1903; 545807 (Box 133)
  - Video 641: Unidentified, CCTV labeled "Peter's Movie at Hong Kong", cuid1904; 545806 (Box 133)
  - Video 642: Unidentified, CCTV labeled "Raw footage 1/28/85", cuid1905; 545805 (Box 133)
  - Video 643: Unidentified, CCTV labeled "TV Commercial Master", cuid1906; 545804 (Box 134)
  - Video 644: Unidentified, CCTV labeled "Workshop Final Edit", cuid1907; 545803 (Box 134)
  - Video 645: Unidentified, CCTV labeled "'The Young Concubine' sample reel", cuid1908; 545802 (Box 134)
  - Video 646: Unidentified, CCTV labeled "'The Young Concubine' sample reel", cuid1909; 545801 (Box 134)
  - Video 647: Unidentified, cuid1910; 545800 (Box 134)
  - Video 648: Unidentified, cuid1911; 545799 (Box 134)
  - Video 649: Unidentified, cuid1912; 545798 (Box 134)
  - Video 650: Unidentified, cuid1913; 545797 (Box 134)
  - Video 651: Unidentified, cuid1914; 545796 (Box 134)
  - Video 652: Asian American International Film Festival (AAIFF), 1979, 2nd, "Same Difference," "Lion Dance," "Odyssey For Peace," CCTV labeled "0B6", cuid1915; 545795 (Box 135)
  - Video 653: Asian American International Film Festival (AAIFF), 1983, 6th, Toshio Matsumoto films: "Connection" (1981), "Relation" (1982), "Shift" (1982), CCTV labeled "0B10", cuid1916; 545794 (Box 135)
  - Video 654: Asian American International Film Festival (AAIFF), 1983, 6th, Films: "Fool's Dance," "So Far From India,," "James Wong Howe," "The Silence," "Spirit of the Dream House," "Playland," "The Beginning," "Hong Kong Dong," The Last Game," "Matrimony, cuid1917; 545793 (Box 135)
  - Video 655: Asian American International Film Festival (AAIFF), 1985, 8th, press conference, camera 1, cuid1918; 545792 (Box 135)
  - Video 656: Asian American International Film Festival (AAIFF), 1985, 8th, press conference, camera 2, cuid1919; 545791 (Box 135)
  - Video 657: Asian American International Film Festival (AAIFF), 1986, 9th, press conference, CCTV labeled "B71", cuid1920; 545790 (Box 135)
  - Video 658: Asian American International Film Festival (AAIFF), 1986, 9th, day 1, Silver Palace, CCTV labeled "B74", cuid1921; 545789 (Box 135)
  - Video 659: Asian American International Film Festival (AAIFF), 1986, 9th, day 1, Rosemary speakers, CCTV labeled "B72", cuid1922; 545788 (Box 135)
  - Video 660: Asian American International Film Festival (AAIFF), 1986, 9th, day 1, portable camera, CCTV labeled "B73", cuid1923; 545787 (Box 135)
  - Video 661: Asian American International Film Festival (AAIFF), 1986, 9th, day 2, speakers, CCTV labeled "B75", cuid1924; 545786 (Box 135)
  - Video 662: Asian American International Film Festival (AAIFF), 1986, 9th, day 3, speakers, CCTV labeled "B76", cuid1925; 545785 (Box 135)
  - Video 663: Asian American International Film Festival (AAIFF), 1986, 9th, day 4, speakers, CCTV labeled "B77", cuid1926; 545784 (Box 135)
  - Video 664: Asian American International Film Festival (AAIFF), 1986, 9th, day 5, speakers, CCTV labeled "B78", cuid1927; 545783 (Box 135)
  - Video 665: Asian American International Film Festival (AAIFF), 1986, 9th, day 5, portable camera, CCTV labeled "B79", cuid1928; 545782 (Box 135)
  - Video 666: Asian American International Film Festival (AAIFF), 1987, 10th, Opening night, tape 1, cuid1929; 545781 (Box 135)
  - Video 667: Asian American International Film Festival (AAIFF), 1987, 10th, day 2, day 3, day 4, cuid1930; 545780 (Box 135)
  - Video 668: Asian American International Film Festival (AAIFF), 1987, 10th, day 5, cuid1931; 545779 (Box 135)
  - Video 669: Asian American International Film Festival (AAIFF), 1987, 10th, day 5, cuid1932; 545778 (Box 135)
  - Video 670: Asian American International Video Festival (AAIVF) Stan Egi, cuid1933; 545777 (Box 135)
  - Video 671: Asian American International Video Festival (AAIVF), 4th, day 1, Private Eyes, CCTV labeled "B64", cuid1934; 545776 (Box 135)
  - Video 672: Asian American International Video Festival (AAIVF), 4th, day 2, Millennium, CCTV labeled "B65", cuid1935; 545775 (Box 135)
  - Video 673: Asian American International Video Festival (AAIVF), 4th, day 3, Millennium, CCTV labeled "B66", cuid1936; 545774 (Box 135)
  - Video 674: Asian American International Video Festival (AAIVF), 4th, day 3, Millennium, portable camera, CCTV labeled "B67", cuid1937; 545773 (Box 135)
  - Video 675: Asian Film Series opening, cuid1938; 545772 (Box 135)
  - Video 676: Asian Film Series, 1986, Panel Discussion: China, 12/14/86, tape 1, cuid1939; 545771 (Box 135)
  - Video 677: Asian Film Series, 1986, Panel Discussion: Japan, 12/14/86, tape 2, cuid1940; 545770 (Box 135)
  - Video 678: Asian Film Series, 1986, Panel Discussion, 12/14/86, tape 3, cuid1941; 545769 (Box 135)
  - Video 679: FFF, 1985, Day 1, Opening, 11/22/85, CCTV labeled "B61", cuid1942; 545768 (Box 135)
  - Video 680: FFF, 1985, Panel Discussion 1, 11/24/85, CCTV labeled "B62", cuid1943; 545767 (Box 135)
  - Video 681: FFF, 1985, Panel Discussion 2, 11/24/85, CCTV labeled "B63", cuid1944; 545766 (Box 135)
  - Video 682: Press Con., CCTV labeled "B23", cuid1945; 545765 (Box 135)
  - Video 683: Press Conference 1987, cuid1946; 545764 (Box 135)
  - Video 684: Asian American Heritage Festival, cuid1947; 545763 (Box 135)
  - Video 685: Asian American Heritage Festival, cuid1948; 545762 (Box 135)
  - Video 686: Asian American Heritage Festival, cuid1949; 545761 (Box 135)
  - Video 687: Asian American Heritage Festival, hand held camera, tape 1, cuid1950; 545760 (Box 135)
  - Video 688: Asian American Heritage Festival, hand held camera, tape 2, cuid1951; 545759 (Box 135)
  - Video 689: Asian American Heritage Festival, left camera, tape 2, cuid1952; 545758 (Box 135)
  - Video 690: Asian American Heritage Festival, left camera, tape 4, cuid1953; 545757 (Box 135)
  - Video 691: Asian American Heritage Festival, left camera, tape 5, cuid1954; 545756 (Box 135)
  - Video 692: Asian American Heritage Festival, right camera, tape 1, cuid1955; 545755 (Box 135)
  - Video 693: Asian American Heritage Festival, right camera, tape 3, folk singer, cuid1956; 545754 (Box 135)
  - Video 694: Asian American Heritage Festival, right camera, tape 4, cuid1957; 545753 (Box 135)
  - Video 695: Asian American Heritage Festival, right camera, tape 6, cuid1958; 545752 (Box 135)
  - Video 696: Cultural Festival, CCTV labeled "B056", cuid1959; 545751 (Box 136)
  - Video 697: Philippines Cinema, CCTV labeled "0B24", cuid1960; 545750 (Box 136)
  - Video 698: AAMHC, Panel 2, 5/2/81, CCTV labeled "B045", cuid1961; 545749 (Box 136)
  - Video 699: AAMHC, Panel 3: Russell Baba, Tape II Children's song,, CCTV labeled "B043", cuid1962; 545748 (Box 136)
  - Video 700: AAMHC, Panel 5, 5/3/81, CCTV labeled "B050", cuid1963; 545747 (Box 136)
  - Video 701: AAMHC, Panel 5 and Fini, 5/3/81, CCTV labeled "B044", cuid1964; 545746 (Box 136)
  - Video 702: Asian American Women Speak Out, 3/31/85, Tape 1 (stationary camera), cuid1965; 545745 (Box 136)
  - Video 703: Asian American Women Speak Out, 3/31/85, Tape 2 (stationary camera), cuid1966; 545744 (Box 136)
  - Video 704: Asian American Women Speak Out, 3/31/85, Tape 3 (stationary camera), interview, cuid1967; 545743 (Box 136)
  - Video 705: Asian American Women Speak Out, 3/31/85, Tape A (sideline), cuid1968; 545742 (Box 136)
  - Video 706: Asian American Women Speak Out, 3/31/85, Tape B (sideline), cuid1969; 545741 (Box 136)
  - Video 707: Asian American Women Speak Out, 3/31/85, Tape C (handheld), cuid1970; 545740 (Box 136)
  - Video 708: Asian Women United/Makasako, Rough Cut #1 -51 min., cuid1971; 545739 (Box 136)
  - Video 709: Aquino Memorial Service, Interview, 8/26/83, cuid1972; 545738 (Box 136)
  - Video 710: Asian American Arts II, Corky and Gene, Interview Part 2, Still photos, cuid1973; 545737 (Box 136)
  - Video 711: CCTV Clothing Demo, CCTV labeled "B128", cuid1974; 545736 (Box 136)
  - Video 712: Chinese Exodus From Vietnam II, CCTV labeled "B022", cuid1975; 545735 (Box 136)
  - Video 713: Cultural Benefit for Hiroshima Victims, CCTV labeled "B151", cuid1976; 545734 (Box 136)
  - Video 714: CCTV Doctor Yang, CCTV labeled "B67", cuid1977; 545733 (Box 136)
  - Video 715: Journey Through New York Chinatown (complete program) (for Nancy Tong), cuid1978; 545732 (Box 136)
  - Video 716: Vincent Chin Memorial, CCTV labeled "B157", cuid1979; 545731 (Box 136)
  - Video 717: Wayne Wang Dim Sum Press Conference, 7/18/85, cuid1980; 545730 (Box 136)
  - Video 718: P.A.L.M. Tagbilaran Religious Day Feast, 5/6/84, tape 1, cuid1981; 545729 (Box 136)
  - Video 719: P.A.L.M. Tagbilaran Religious Day Feast, 5/6/84, tape 2, cuid1982; 545728 (Box 136)
  - Video 720: P.A.L.M. presents: Filipino Writers in Exile: Basement workshop reading/ 17 April 1984, Faigao, Francia, Florentine, Rosca, cuid1983; 545727 (Box 136)
  - Video 721: Disarmament tape, CCTV labeled "B003", cuid1984; 545726 (Box 136)
  - Video 722: Japanese American hearings: San Francisco Commission on Wartime Relocation, CCTV labeled "B049", cuid1985; 545725 (Box 136)
  - Video 723: Redress and reparations for Japanese internment, CCTV labeled "B59", cuid1986; 545724 (Box 136)
  - Video 724: Redress and reparations for Japanese internment interview, CCTV labeled "B70", cuid1987; 545723 (Box 136)
  - Video 725: Redress and reparations for Japanese internment investigation, cuid1988; 545722 (Box 136)
  - Video 726: Redress and reparations for Japanese internment investigation, cuid1989; 545721 (Box 136)
  - Video 727: Redress and reparations for Japanese internment press conference, CCTV labeled "B128", cuid1990; 545720 (Box 136)
  - Video 728: Redress and reparations for Japanese internment reception, cuid1991; 545719 (Box 136)
  - Video 729: Stereotypes, CCTV labeled "B023", cuid1992; 545718 (Box 136)
  - Video 730: Stereotype excerpt "Pearls," CCTV labeled "B002", cuid1993; 545717 (Box 136)
  - Video 731: Stereotypes in the Media: TV excerpts, CCTV labeled "B024", cuid1994; 545716 (Box 136)
  - Video 732: Stereotypes in the Media: Commission against Fort Apache demonstration, CCTV labeled "B040", cuid1995; 545715 (Box 136)
  - Video 733: Stereotypes in the Media: Charlie Chan demonstration, CCTV labeled "B041", cuid1996; 545714 (Box 136)
  - Video 734: Charlie Chan demonstration, CCTV labeled "B042", cuid1997; 545713 (Box 136)
  - Video 735: ACV Philippino Interview, CCTV labeled "B34", cuid1998; 545712 (Box 136)
  - Video 736: Korean-Am interview, cuid1999; 545711 (Box 136)
  - Video 737: Jessica's Performance, CCTV labeled "B106", cuid2000; 545710 (Box 136)
  - Video 738: Group 3, second project: Radio DJ, cuid2001; 545709 (Box 136)
  - Video 739: Group I, Project II, tape II: Performance (Marlena), cuid2002; 545708 (Box 136)
  - Video 740: Mr. Carter, tape 1, CCTV labeled "B038", cuid2003; 545707 (Box 137)
  - Video 741: Mr. Carter, tape 2, CCTV labeled "B039", cuid2004; 545706 (Box 137)
  - Video 742: Mrs. Carter #1, CCTV labeled "B035", cuid2005; 545705 (Box 137)
  - Video 743: Mrs. Carter #2, CCTV labeled "B036", cuid2006; 545704 (Box 137)
  - Video 744: Ezra Vogel interview: "Japan as number 1," camera #1, Rene Tajima, 11/12, CCTV labeled "B118", cuid2007; 545703 (Box 137)
  - Video 745: Ezra Vogel interview: "Japan as number 1," camera #2, Rene Tajima, 11/12, CCTV labeled "B103", cuid2008; 545702 (Box 137)
  - Video 746: Demonstrations in New York for and against Chiang's Presidency in Taiwan, 5/20/78, CCTV labeled "B030", cuid2009; 545701 (Box 137)
  - Video 747: Presentation(?), cuid2010; 545700 (Box 137)
  - Video 748: Boycott Year of the Dragon, 8/16/85, cuid2011; 545699 (Box 137)
  - Video 749: Asian American Experience: Senior Center Building (12/15), Alan Cohen (1-185), Aleutian Woman (185-800), CCTV labeled "B22, cuid2012; 545698 (Box 137)
  - Video 750: Mutya Gener, K.C.K., CCTV labeled "B10", cuid2013; 545697 (Box 137)
  - Video 751: Support for US-China Diplomatic Normalization I, CCTV labeled "B032", cuid2014; 545696 (Box 137)
  - Video 752: Against for US-China Diplomatic Normalization, CCTV labeled "B031", cuid2015; 545695 (Box 137)
  - Video 753: F.O.B. by David Henry Hwang, tape 1, CCTV labeled "B037", cuid2016; 545694 (Box 137)
  - Video 754: F.O.B. by David Henry Hwang, tape 2, CCTV labeled "B034", cuid2017; 545693 (Box 137)
  - Video 755: Sun Rise play, CCTV labeled "B29", cuid2018; 545692 (Box 137)
  - Video 756:Mako, lead actor from Hito Hata: Raise the Banner, CCTV labeled "B28", cuid2019; 545691 (Box 137)
  - Video 757: Mako and Hito Hata Interview, 3/28/81, CCTV labeled "B39", cuid2020; 545690 (Box 137)
  - Video 758: Roman Tam and Michelle Yim at the Tropicana, Christmas 1982, tape 1, CCTV labeled "B047", cuid2021; 545689 (Box 137)
  - Video 759: Roman Tam and Michelle Yim at the Tropicana, Christmas 1982, tape 2, CCTV labeled "B048", cuid2022; 545688 (Box 137)
  - Video 760: Cinevue Presents Arnie Wong, 3/9/86, cuid2023; 545687 (Box 137)
  - Video 761:Workshop Dinner, 10/83: 1st part drama, 2nd part dinner, cuid2024; 545686 (Box 137)
  - Video 762: P.S. Henry Street Grade 2 Students Nutrition Show, cuid2025; 545685 (Box 137)
  - Video 763: Voting Machine demonstration, 11/5/84, camera original, cuid2026; 545684 (Box 137)
  - Video 764: Canadians of Chinese Heritage history, CCTV labeled "B121", cuid2027; 545683 (Box 137)
  - Video 765: Chinese Exodus from Vietnam I, CCTV labeled "B21", cuid2028; 545682 (Box 137)
  - Video 766: Two Comedians, Interior, tape C, continuous L.S., cuid2029; 545681 (Box 137)
  - Video 767: Two Comedians, Interior, tape B, continuous L.S., cuid2030; 545680 (Box 137)
  - Video 768: Philip and Henry, CCTV labeled "B43", cuid2031; 545679 (Box 137)
  - Video 769: Philip Kon Golanda, CCTV labeled "B77", cuid2032; 545678 (Box 137)
  - Video 770: Peter, Paul, Mary, CCTV labeled "B149", cuid2033; 545677 (Box 137)
  - Video 771: Jacob, cuid2034; 545676 (Box 137)
  - Video 772: Jane Fonda, cuid2035; 545675 (Box 137)
  - Video 773: Chinese concert, cuid2036; 545674 (Box 138)
  - Video 774: Chinese concert, cuid2037; 545673 (Box 138)
  - Video 775: Chinese music: 1) pipa, 2) violin, 3) music, 4) singing, 5) flute, cuid2038; 545672 (Box 138)
  - Video 776: Chinese Music Ensemble of New York I, CCTV labeled "B051", cuid2039; 545671 (Box 138)
  - Video 777: Chinese Music Ensemble of New York II, CCTV labeled "B052", cuid2040; 545670 (Box 138)
  - Video 778: Chinese Opera, cuid2041; 545669 (Box 138)
  - Video 779: Chinese singers (AC), cuid2042; 545668 (Box 138)
  - Video 780: Kim Lai Wah Cantonese Opera I, CCTV labeled "B027", cuid2043; 545667 (Box 138)
  - Video 781: Kim Lai Wah Cantonese Opera II, CCTV labeled "B028", cuid2044; 545666 (Box 138)
  - Video 782: Kim Lai Wah Cantonese Opera III, CCTV labeled "B029", cuid2045; 545665 (Box 138)
  - Video 783: Opera/Parade/Program, cuid2046; 545664 (Box 138)
  - Video 784: Peking Opera, CCTV labeled "B104", cuid2047; 545663 (Box 138)
  - Video 785: Traditional Chinese music, cuid2048; 545662 (Box 138)
  - Video 786: Asian American Dance Theater, CCTV labeled "B009", cuid2049; 545661 (Box 138)
  - Video 787: Asian American Dance Theater, CCTV labeled "B008", cuid2050; 545660 (Box 138)
  - Video 788: Asian American Dance Theater (I), 4/22/78, CCTV labeled "B006", cuid2051; 545659 (Box 138)
  - Video 789: Asian American Dance Theater (II), 4/22/78, CCTV labeled "B007", cuid2052; 545658 (Box 138)
  - Video 790: Asian American Dance Theater, Riverside Dance Concert, April '83, cuid2053; 545657 (Box 138)
  - Video 791: Chen and Dancers, H.T. Dance Company, CCTV labeled "B025", cuid2054; 545656 (Box 138)
  - Video 792: Chiang Ching Dance Company, I, CCTV labeled "B010", cuid2055; 545655 (Box 138)
  - Video 793: Chiang Ching Dance Company, II, CCTV labeled "B011", cuid2056; 545654 (Box 138)
  - Video 794:Hsu Shuh Ying Dance Workshop, CCTV labeled "B057", cuid2057; 545653 (Box 138)
  - Video 795: Taiko Drums Amy Kato, Chris Komuro (10 minutes), cuid2058; 545652 (Box 138)
  - Video 796: Asian American experience: Charlie Chin in concert, 5/22, CCTV labeled "B56", cuid2059; 545651 (Box 138)
  - Video 797: Charlie Chin interview, cuid2060; 545650 (Box 138)
  - Video 798: Charlie Chin, CCTV labeled "B001", cuid2061; 545649 (Box 138)
  - Video 799: Charlie Chin and Joanne, 4/20/78, CCTV labeled "B026", cuid2062; 545648 (Box 138)
  - Video 800: Asian American Experience: Charlie Chin concert, 5/22, tape 8, CCTV labeled "B57", cuid2063; 545647 (Box 138)
  - Video 801: Asian American Experience: Asian American artists-Zignal rehearsal, 1/30/80, tape 3, cuid2064; 545646 (Box 138)
  - Video 802: Asian American Experience: Asian American artists-Zignal rehearsal, 1/30/80, tape 4, cuid2065; 545645 (Box 138)
  - Video 803: Asian American culture, tape 6, cuid2066; 545644 (Box 138)
  - Video 804: People's Republic of China (PRC) Troupe #1, cuid2067; 545643 (Box 138)
  - Video 805: People's Republic of China (PRC) Troupe#2, cuid2068; 545642 (Box 138)
  - Video 806: Dangerous Encounters of the First King (1979) by Radio Television Hong Kong, CCTV labeled "B005", cuid2069; 545641 (Box 139)
  - Video 807: Loose Pages Bond (1979), Dir. Chris Choy, CCTV labeled "B001", cuid2070; 545640 (Box 139)
  - Video 808: The New Wife (1968), cuid2071; 545639 (Box 139)
  - Video 809: Regret for the Past, tape 1, CCTV labeled "B007", cuid2072; 545638 (Box 139)
  - Video 810: Regret for the Past, tape II, CCTV labeled "B008", cuid2073; 545637 (Box 139)
  - Video 811: Rickshaw Boy (1980), CCTV labeled "B017", cuid2074; 545636 (Box 139)
  - Video 812: Teahouse (1982), CCTV labeled "B016", cuid2075; 545635 (Box 139)
  - Video 813: Wild Children (1977) by Radio Television Hong Kong, CCTV labeled "B004", cuid2076; 545634 (Box 139)
  - Video 814: Willful Murder (1981), CCTV labeled "B014", cuid2077; 545633 (Box 139)
  - Video 815: An American Story, Part I, CCTV labeled "B004, cuid2078; 545632 (Box 139)
  - Video 816: An American Story, Part II, CCTV labeled "B005, cuid2079; 545631 (Box 139)
  - Video 817: And the Soul Shall Dance, CCTV labeled "B018", cuid2080; 545630 (Box 139)
  - Video 818: And the Soul Shall Dance, CCTV labeled "B019", cuid2081; 545629 (Box 139)
  - Video 819: Arakawa, Manilatown Lives (1986), The Year of the Ox (1973), Snipers in the Trees (1985), cuid2082; 545628 (Box 139)
  - Video 820: Boat People, CCTV labeled "B012", cuid2083; 545627 (Box 139)
  - Video 821: Bullet Headed Bird II, CCTV labeled "B102", cuid2084; 545626 (Box 139)
  - Video 822: Butterfly Love #1, CCTV labeled "B015", cuid2085; 545625 (Box 139)
  - Video 823: Butterfly Love #2, CCTV labeled "B016", cuid2086; 545624 (Box 139)